The unspoken words hiding inside your heart,
Set them free and raise your voice
Be the brightest version of yourself
and take hold of all the things you love
Winners and losers don't matter
Come let's join hands
Hey jump! The party's just getting started!
Hey! Let's go, it's party time!
Let's dance with 1,2,3! Into the future! We're together forever
We're never ever going to give up, we swear on that
LEt's sing "I'll do my best"! Tomorrow will be even brighter
Cyalume Change!
Muster up your courage and search for joy
and take over PriPara!
LEt's sing "I'll do my best"! Tomorrow will be even brighter
Muster up your courage and search for joy
and take over PriPara!